Guide to the Charles Rivers Photographs and Scrapbooks TAM.260
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Negatives, 1921-1989
  - Sunseries II:F: Worksites, 1921-1929
    - Keeping up with the news during lunch. Chrysler [Building], 1929 (Box 1, Item 3)
    - Iron Worker, Chrysler Building, 1929 (Box 1, Item 2)
    - NYC as viewed from the Chrysler Building during construction, 1929 (Box 1, Item 1)
    - NYC as viewed from the Chrysler Building during construction, 1929 (Box 1, Item 39)
  - Subseries II:G: Miscellaneous Events, 1929-1989
    - Sharing [Horse and birds drinking water on the street], undated (Box 1, Item 503)
    - Straus Memorial [Sculpture/memorial for Ida and Isidor Straus at Straus Park, 107th and Broadway, NYC], undated (Box 1, Item 494)
    - Ludlow Massacre [Monument], undated (Box 1, Item 466)
    - Pathe [Studio?] Fire, [Dec 10, 1929?] (Box 1, Item 72)
    - Funeral of Alfred Leni, black worker shot in Harlem [Sign/banner: "Pledge to carry on the fight against boss …beside the body of Alfred Leni …Murdered by Police at Harlem anti-lynch."], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 486)
    - Textile Mill--North Carolina, 1930 (Box 1, Item 7)
    - Federal Food Distribution--Brooklyn, 1934 (Box 1, Item 484)
    - Derelict City--South Bronx, [1970s?] (Box 1, Item 471)
    - Dialogue [2 horses near a subway entrance], [1970s?] (Box 1, Item 479)
    - Decay of a City--NY, [1970s?] (Box 1, Item 451)
    - Washington Square [two men in wheelchairs], [1970s?] (Box 1, Item 461)
    - Amon Carter Museum Fort Worth, Texas, [1980s?] (Box 1, Item 442)
    - Dakota [Apartment] Building; City Scene, NYC, [1980?] (Box 1, Item 469)
    - [John Lennon's Death: Dakota Apartment Building], [1980?] (Box 1, Item 476)
    - [John Lennon's Death: Dakota Apartment Building], [1980?] (Box 1, Item 475)
    - John Lennon--Entrance to his home where he was murdered, and Central Park meeting following his death, 1980 (Box 1, Item 477)
    - Jim Crow Section - Charlotte, NC, undated (Box 1, Item 505)
- Series III: Photographic Prints and Clippings, 1929-1988
  - Clippings, 1938-1949 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University Student Strike, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Construction (I), 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Construction (II), 1929-1930 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Demonstrations: Anti-Nuclear, 1979-1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Demonstrations: Anti-War (I), 1934 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Demonstrations: Anti-War (II), 1933-1936; 1970s (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Demonstrations: General, 1930-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Demonstrations: General (Includes Greece, Students, May Day), 1930s, 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Demonstrations: Greece, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Labor, 1960, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1934, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (Includes Pete Seeger), 1930, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)